export const Questions = [{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "You should not use any of the JavaScript reserved keyword as variable name.",
    optionB: "JavaScript variable names should not start with a numeral (0-9).",
    optionC: "Both of the above.",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "C",
    hint: "Both of the above options are correct.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "How can you get the type of arguments passed to a function?",
    optionA: "using typeof operator",
    optionB: "using getType function",
    optionC: "Both of the above.",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "Using typeof operator, we can get the type of arguments passed to a function.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
    optionA: "characterAt()",
    optionB: "getCharAt()",
    optionC: "charAt()",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "C",
    hint: "charAt() method returns the character at the specified index.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "All user-defined objects and built-in objects are descendants of an object called Object?",
    optionA: "true",
    optionB: "false",
    optionC: "",
    optionD: "",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "All user-defined objects and built-in objects are descendants of an object called Object.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of Boolean object returns the primitive value of the Boolean object?",
    optionA: "toSource()",
    optionB: "valueOf()",
    optionC: "toString()",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "valueOf() − Returns the primitive value of the Boolean object.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of String object returns the index within the calling String object of the last occurrence of the specified value?",
    optionA: "lastIndexOf()",
    optionB: "search()",
    optionC: "substr()",
    optionD: "indexOf()",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "lastIndexOf() − Returns the index within the calling String object of the last occurrence of the specified value, or -1 if not found.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to upper case?",
    optionA: "toLocaleUpperCase()",
    optionB: "toUpperCase()",
    optionC: "toString()",
    optionD: "substring()",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "toUpperCase() − Returns the calling string value converted to upper case.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in fixed-pitch font as if it were in a <tt> tag?",
    optionA: "fixed()",
    optionB: "big()",
    optionC: "blink()",
    optionD: "bold()",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "fixed() − Causes a string to be displayed in fixed-pitch font as if it were in a <tt> tag.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of Array object calls a function for each element in the array?",
    optionA: "concat()",
    optionB: "every()",
    optionC: "filter()",
    optionD: "forEach()",
    answer: "D",
    hint: "forEach() − Calls a function for each element in the array.",
},
{
    topic: "Javascript",
    prompt: "Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
    optionA: "toSource()",
    optionB: "splice()",
    optionC: "toString()",
    optionD: "unshift()",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "toSource() − Represents the source code of an object.",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "React is mainly used for building",
    optionA: "Database",
    optionB: "Connectivity",
    optionC: " User interface",
    optionD: " Design Platform",
    answer: "C",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "The lifecycle methods are mainly used for",
    optionA: " keeping track of event history",
    optionB: " enhancing components",
    optionC: " freeing up resources",
    optionD: " none of the above",
    answer: "C",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "Which is the right way of accessing a function fetch() from an h1 element in JSX?",
    optionA: " <h1>{fetch()}</h1>",
    // eslint-disable-next-line no-template-curly-in-string
    optionB: " <h1>${fetch()}</h1>",
    optionC: " <h1>{fetch}</h1>",
    // eslint-disable-next-line no-template-curly-in-string
    optionD: " <h1>${fetch}</h1>",
    answer: "A",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "Which of the following methods in a React Component should be overridden to stop the component from updating?",
    optionA: " willComponentUpdate",
    optionB: "shouldComponentUpdate",
    optionC: "componentDidUpdate",
    optionD: "componentDidMount",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "Which of the following methods in a React Component is called after the component is rendered for the first time?",
    optionA: "componentDidUpdate",
    optionB: "componentDidMount",
    optionC: " componentMounted",
    optionD: "componentUpdated",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "Which of the following is the correct syntax for a button click event handler foo?",
    optionA: " <button onclick={this.foo()}>",
    optionB: " <button onclick={this.foo}>",
    optionC: " <button onClick={this.foo()}>",
    optionD: " <button onClick={this.foo}>",
    answer: "D",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "What will happen if you call setState() inside render() method?",
    optionA: "Repetitive output appears on the screen",
    optionB: " Duplicate key error",
    optionC: " Stack overflow error",
    optionD: " Nothing happens",
    answer: "C",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "How do you write an inline style which specifies the font-size:12px and color:red; in JSX?",
    optionA: "style={{font-size:12,color:'red'}}",
    optionB: " style={{fontSize:'12px',color:'red'}}",
    optionC: " style={fontSize:'12px',color:'red'}",
    optionD: " style={{font-size:12px,color:'red'}}",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "What advantages does ReactJS have?",
    optionA: " Increases the application’s performance with Virtual DOM",
    optionB: " JSX makes a code that is easy to read and write",
    optionC: " It renders both on client and server side",
    optionD: " All of the above",
    answer: "D",
    hint: "",
},
{
    topic: "React",
    prompt: "What is state in React?",
    optionA: " A persistant storage.",
    optionB: " An internal data store (object) of a component.",
    optionC: "",
    optionD: "",
    answer: "B",
    hint: "",
},
]